(Sheldon:)Tom is a paramedic
with the fire department.
(Sheldon:)He's going to med school.
(Sheldon:)Uh, he likes the outdoors
and, uh, strong women who initiate sex.
(Leonard:)Really, really bad.
(Sheldon:)I'm surprised you struck out with Penny.
Apparently, she's a big old five.
- Sheldon, what do you want?
- Oh, good, you got my note.
(Sheldon:)Penny, I'd like you to meet Tom.
Uh, Penny, this is Tom.
(Sheldon:)- Tom, may I present Penny.
- Hi, Penny.
Hi, as long as I'm here, I'm on a quest with
newbs, don't know what they're doing.
Got one assassin, three spell casters,
no tank.
- Can we talk later?
- No, I need you now.
(Sheldon:)Wouldn't you prefer
to socialize with Tom...
(Sheldon:)...who is a sexually passive
outdoorsman?
- Whatever, I'll figure it out myself.
- Bye, Penny.
(Tom:)I'm sorry, dude,
she didn't look anything like her picture.
(Leonard:)They never do.
HOWARD:
Hello, fair Penny.
PENNY: Who are you?
HOWARD: It is I, Sir Howard of Wolowitz.
(Warrior:)Can I interest you
in an afternoon of spirited questing...
(Warrior:)...followed by a flagon of ale
at yon virtual tavern?
PENNY:
Yeah, sure, why not?
(Penny:)Oh, my God, I need help.